clari.com 2018-12-30

# Clari Privacy Policy - Clari

**Updated May 29, 2018**

#### Revision history

  * May 29, 2018: Added reference to Clari GDPR web link and clarified policy change notification.
  * May 21, 2018: Clarified our disclosure policy to state that information will only be disclosed when required by public authorities or the law
  * February 27, 2018: Added specific language to comply with Google’s User Data Policy, clarifying how Clari “accesses, uses, stores, or shares Google user data”

#### The Policy

Clari, Inc. ("Clari") knows that you care about how your corporate and personal information is used and shared - and we take your privacy seriously. This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") covers Clari's treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") and enterprise information ("Enterprise Information") (such as: CRM data, files, email/calendar information, and contacts) that you submit, or Clari otherwise gathers, when you access or use the Service. Together, Personal Information and Enterprise Information will be referred to as "Information".

By using the [www.clari.com](https://www.clari.com/) website ("Site") or any of our Clari applications available via the application URL: app.clari.com and the Clari mobile applications: Clari Mobile and Clari Connect (collectively, the "Service") you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you consent that we will collect, use, and share your information as set forth below. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the sole purpose of providing the service for which your organization (Clari’s “Client”) has engaged Clari. Specific services offered are governed by the Clari Master Service Agreement and business terms for the items purchased by the Client per the Order Agreement.

Clari participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Clari is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, respectively, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Frameworks, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>

Clari is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Frameworks, and for any subsequent transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Clari complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, Clari is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Clari may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including requests to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the [Privacy Shield website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint), you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

#### EU Personal Data

If you are located in the EU, United Kingdom, Lichtenstein, Norway, or Iceland, you may have additional rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”). For more information about Clari’s compliance with GDPR, please visit [our page](https://www.clari.com/gdpr) dedicated to GDPR.

#### What Information Does Clari Collect?

When you visit the Site and express an interest in obtaining additional information about Clari or the Service, or register to receive marketing materials, event registrations or any other form submission tools that collect your personal contact information such as name, company name, address, phone number and email address (“Required Contact Information”), Clari collects this personal information.

By downloading and enabling the Service, you are authorizing Clari to access and store all of the foregoing types of Information:

  * Information you submit as part of the registration process such as your name and email address
  * Information you elect to submit (including, without limitation, any text, documents, images or other content or materials) to any areas of the Service that are accessible by other Service users within your organization ("User Submissions"). Such information may be shared with other Services users within your organization - as elected by you via the Service. For example, if you post a photo as part of a deal channel, that may be visible to other Service users within your organization. We endeavor to make sure the Service's functionality puts you on reasonable notice as to the scope of an intended submission.
  * Information that Clari may obtain from third-party services (both Personal and Enterprise Information, such as CRM data, files, email/calendar information, and contacts) that Clari requires for the operation of the Clari service.
  * For Google Apps/Gmail users, Clari collects email and calendar metadata for the sole business-related use of the user and Clari’s Client. Such information is never provided or disclosed to anyone other than the user and users specifically authorized by the Client.

You acknowledge and agree that you will not (i) provide us with any information that you do not have the right to provide, or (ii) share, via the Service, any information you do not have the right to share (such as information that is confidential to any third party and that you are not authorized to share with your intended recipients).

Note that certain features of the Service may allow you to import information from third party services (such as Salesforce) ("Third Party Services"). By requesting that Clari import such information, you authorize Clari to use your Third Party Service username and password to access the applicable Third Party Service Account. This authentication process is managed by the applicable Third Party Service provider. Clari will not use your Third Party Service account credentials for any other purpose.

##### Information We Collect Automatically

Whenever you interact with our Service, we may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser or device, which may include your IP address, device identification, "cookie" information, web beacons, the type of browser and/or device you're using to access our Service, domain name server and the page or feature you requested (“tracking information”), in order to analyze product usage patterns. In addition, when using the Site, Clari and its partners may use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. "Cookies" are identifiers we transfer to your browser or device that allow us to recognize your browser or device and tell us how and when pages and features in our Service are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or device to prevent or limit your device's acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our features. When we collect the usage information described in this paragraph, we only use this data in aggregate form. For example, this aggregate data can tell us how often users use a particular feature of the Service, and we can use that knowledge to make the Service valuable to as many users as possible.

##### Social Media Features

The Company’s Web sites may use social media features, such as the Facebook ‘like’ button (“Social Media Features”). These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on the Company’s Web site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. You may be given the option by such Social Media Features to post information about your activities on the Company’s Web site to a profile page of yours that is provided by a third party Social Media network in order to share with others within your network. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Company’s Web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the relevant Social Media Features.

##### Do Not Track

Currently, various browsers — including Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari — offer a “do not track” or “DNT” option that relies on a technology known as a DNT header, which sends a signal to Web sites’ visited by the user about the user's browser DNT preference setting. Salesforce does not currently commit to responding to browsers' DNT signals with respect to the Company's Web sites, in part, because no common industry standard for DNT has been adopted by industry groups, technology companies or regulators, including no consistent standard of interpreting user intent. Salesforce takes privacy and meaningful choice seriously and will make efforts to continue to monitor developments around DNT browser technology and the implementation of a standard.

##### Mobile Application Usage

When you download our mobile applications and use them to access our Services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use and operating system version. We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within the mobile application.

##### How Does Clari Use the Information It Collects?

Clari uses your Information as follows:

  * To operate and maintain the Service (such as, for the purposes of fixing malfunctions, testing our security systems, etc.).
  * To provide you with the features, functions and benefits of the Service.
  * To enhance, improve and further develop the Service (such as, creating new features or functions, refining the user experience, increasing Service technical performance, etc.).
  * We will use your contact information to provide you with notices related to your use of the Service.
  * We will use your contact information (such as, your email address) to provide you with training and marketing emails. You can opt-out of receiving certain types of training and marketing emails - but in such case you may not receive the full benefit of the Service. Opting-out can be done by clicking the "manage email settings" link at the bottom of every email.
  * To help personalize the Service experience for you (such as, remembering your information so you will not have to enter it each time you use the Service).
  * And for the other purposes referenced in the "Will Clari Share Any of the Information it Receives" section below (such as, for the purposes of legal compliance).
  * In addition, Required Contact Information collected when you visit the Site is used as follows:
  * Marketing activities such as emails, promotional mail designed to generate leads
  * Inform you of upcoming events, product or service updates
  * Provide access to areas of the Site that is not normally available

#### Will Clari Share Any of the Information It Receives?

To the limited extent we collect Information - we neither rent nor sell your Information to anyone. We share your Information only as described below.

##### Within Your Organization

As mentioned above - certain of your Enterprise Information may be shared internally with other members of your organization.

##### Recipient of User Submissions

As mentioned above - your User Submissions may be shared with other Service users within your organization through normal usage of the service.

##### Third Parties

We may employ third parties for the purpose of providing our product and services to you. Your information may be accessed by these third parties in the performance of their services. These services may include usage tracking service such as Mixpanel, log service such as SumoLogic or platform service provider such as Amazon Web Service (AWS). Third parties may not use your information for any purpose other than to assist with providing our services to you.

Clari may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients. Currently, no such transfers occur and any future third party that we engage will be listed in this section.

##### Business Transfers

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Clari, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Clari goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Clari may continue to use your Information as set forth in this policy.

##### Protection of Clari and Others

We may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including meeting national security or law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. 

##### With Your Consent

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

##### Relationship to Your Organization

Clari processes Information about you as authorized by your Organization (usually, your employer). Your organization is Clari's Client (“Client”) and is the data controller. When the Client signs up to the terms as stated in the governing Master Service Agreement, they agree to transfer certain rights to your Information to Clari. Clari will not act as an arbiter of data privacy issues that may arise between you and your organization during this process.

#### What You Can Do to Your Personal Information?

##### Editing Your Profile

Upon request, Clari will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. To request this information please contact us at privacy@clari.com. If you wish to access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information, please contact us at privacy@clari.com. Clari has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes within its Service. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to Clari's Client (the data controller). If the Client requests Clari to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 days. If as an individual, you wish to identify the specific Client who is acting as the data controller of your Information, please contact privacy@clari.com and we will provide their contact information subject to Clari receiving approval of release of that information from the data controller.

##### Deleting Your Account

You can delete your account by sending an email to support@clari.com. Subject to the "Limitations on Deletion" section below, when you request us to delete your account for the Service, your data may be permanently deleted from our servers and access to your account will be disabled. We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

Clari will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. Clari will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

##### Limitations on Deletion

In addition, copies of your information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been publicly published by you or otherwise shared by you with others (such as your User Submissions).

We may also indefinitely retain and use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally.

We may also retain Information collected by Third Party usage tracking services in aggregate form, for the purposes of maintaining historical information on usage of our services.

##### Laws and Regulations

We may also retain your Information to the extent required to comply with (or we deem it reasonable in light of) any laws or regulations.

##### California Residents

Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please mail a written request to the Clari (contact info below).

##### Choice

We partner with a third party to display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/), or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

You may sign-up to receive email or newsletter or other communications from us. If you would like to discontinue receiving this information, you may update your email preferences by using the "Unsubscribe" link found in emails we send to you or by contacting us at [support@clari.com](mailto:support@clari.com).

We collect information for our Clients, if you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly.

#### What About Third-Party Services Clari Connects To?

Clari links to other services, such as Salesforce. Clari does not access any information from these third-party services without your authorization, or by the authorization of your organization. You grant Clari this authorization when you connect these services to Clari, or when your organization's IT team authorizes these connections on your behalf. To opt out of connecting to these services, contact your organization.

#### How We Protect Your Information

Clari takes robust information security measures to protect your Information and to limit the risk that it will be accessed without authorization, including use of certain industry standard technologies and practices. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. That said, we cannot guarantee the security of such Information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. No security system is perfect - so your use of the Service is at your own risk.

If we learn of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you via email, phone, physical mail, or by a posting on your Service account page - so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Pursuant to our Terms of Service you have consented to receive such notice by electronic means (provided that such consent is void where prohibited by applicable law). To receive a free written notice of a security breach, or if you have any questions about the security of the Service, please contact us at info@clari.com

In addition to the security measures referenced above, your Service account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last changed on the date set forth at the top of the policy. We're constantly trying to improve the Service, so we may need to change this Privacy Policy from time to time as well, but we will alert you to changes by placing a revision notice on this page, and if changes are significant, by sending you an email, providing a notification through your Service account, or by some other means. In addition, we will also edit the date at the top of this policy to reflect the date of the changes. Please note that if you've opted not to receive legal notice emails from us (or you haven't provided us with your email address), those legal notices will still govern your use of the Service, and you are still responsible for reading and understanding them. If you use the Service after any changes to the Privacy Policy have been posted, that means you agree to all of the changes. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected.

#### Contacting Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy practices, please contact us at phone: (650) 265-2111, email: [privacy@clari.com](mailto:privacy@clari.com) or: Clari Inc., 1154 Sonora Court, Sunnyvale, CA 94086
